govbid.org 2019-10-10

# Terms & Conditions - Gov.Bid

When you use our services, you’re trusting us with your information, GB Contract Trading LLC and its affiliates (collectively, "GOVBID", “G.B.P”, “Ourselves”, “We” and "Us", refers to our Company. “Party”, “Parties”, or “Us”) respect your privacy. Please read the following to learn more about our Privacy Policy ("this Policy"). This Policy applies to Individuals who access and use the GOVBID website, products, information generated from users trough the operation of service requests or services that display or provide links to this Policy.

This Policy describes how GOVBID processe, manage and delete your personal data, but it may not address all possible data processing scenarios. GOVBID may inform you of product- or service-specific data collection through supplementary policies or notices provided before collection.

**This Policy describes:**  
[11\. Personal Information about other people that you provide to us](https://govbid.org/terms_uses#p11)  

Personal data means any data that, either on its own or combined with other data, that can be used to identify a real person. You directly provide us with such data when you use our websites, products, services or interact with us. For example, creating a GOVBID account or, contact us for support.

We may also obtain data by monitoring how you interact with our websites or services. For example, we may use technologies like cookies or receive client data from software running on your device such as IP address, Device type (Desktop/Phone) and browser name.

 _We may use your Personal Information for the following purposes:_  

  * To enter into or carry out contracts of various kinds
  * To process digital fund transfers and conversions
  * To provide you with mediator brokerage and other services available on our platforms
  * To contact you regarding new features and functionality that may be of interest to you
  * To deal with any requests or inquiries you may have
  * To mitigate network attacks and prevent data breach
  * To pursue legitimate interests, including to carry out, monitor and analyze our business or operations
  * To conduct monitoring by us using various methods, including: (i) the use of supervised automated network monitoring tools or (ii) nonsensitive aggregate data manual checkups or (iii) specific monitoring of users anomalous generated data for example in relation to fraud investigations, malicious activity, resource access requests, or (iv) data tracking, aggregation and analysis tools that pull data from various data sources to draw connections and detect behavioral patterns, interactions or preferences for analysis (including predictive analysis) or (v) using other similar monitoring technology that may become available or upgraded from time to time.

We collect information from you when you register on our site, make a deposit, purchase a contract, request a withdrawal, contact us for support, when you leave feedback and when an individual registers on our website using your referral link.

We retrieve data (IP/Region/Device/BrowserName) from software running on your device, The personal data we collect during registration setup includes name, phone number, social links, email addresses, login information (account and password), photos, payment address and answers to security questions. We also collect the information you provide to us and the content of messages you send us, such as questions or information you provide for customer service support. Before using GOVBID’s services, you will need to provide personal data. In some cases, you may be able to opt not to disclose your personal data to GOVBID. However, not providing GOVBID with certain data may mean that we cannot provide you certain services or respond to an issue that you have raised.

We may share user-generated Information in the following circumstances:  
We may share your Personal Information between GOVBID Entities on a confidential basis as allowed by applicable law or where required for the purpose of providing products or services, payment processing, and other business purposes.

We are committed to protecting your privacy. Authorized employees within the company on a need to know basis only use any information collected from individual customers. We constantly review our systems and data to ensure the best possible service to our customers. We will not sell, share, or rent your personal information to any third party or use your e-mail address for unsolicited mail. Any emails sent by this Company will only be in connection with the provision of agreed services and products. All the data given by a member to GB CONTRACT TRADING LLC will be only privately used and not disclosed to any third parties.

Some of our services let you share information with other people, and you have control over what information is publicly displayed. For example, writing a feedback on our services, here information you share is visible publicly along with payout and team statics. Individuals who screen capture videos or take screenshots to be shared on youtube, skype, telegram, and other similar services should remember when you share information publicly, your content may become accessible through search engines. If you voluntarily submit private and sensitive information through similar services as mentioned above, we are not responsible for such and have no control over the privacy and data security practices of our customers, which may differ from those set forth in this Privacy Statement.

When it comes to the management of your assets, nothing gets close to the level of attention we put at making sure your operations are always processing safely.  
We have designed a multiple-phase security process, intending to provide the utmost protection level for our users. It consists of an (i) automatic filtration system, (ii) manual and computerized payment requests investigation system and (iii) other types of data analysis and monitoring systems that continuously protect your information.   
Our data is managed and processed with strong security features (both hardware and software) that meet the requirements of the strictest countries and exceed the requirements of the rest. This is reflected in our ability to uphold the standards required by the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).

The insights we gain from maintaining our services help us detect and automatically block security threats from ever reaching you. And if we do detect something risky that we think you should know about, we’ll notify you and help guide you through steps to stay better protected.

Our websites are not directed at children. We do not knowingly collect Personal Data from Children or Minors under the age of 18. If you are a parent or guardian and believe your child has provided us with Personal Data without your consent, please contact us by using the information in the “Contacting us” section, below, and we will take steps to delete such Personal Data from our systems.

We securely retain your Personal Information in an identifiable form following our internal policies which establish general standards and procedures regarding the retention, handling, and disposition of your Personal Information. Personal Information is retained for as long as necessary to meet legal, regulatory and business requirements. Retention periods may be extended if we are required to preserve your Personal Information in connection with fraud investigations and proceedings.

If you provide Personal Information to us about someone else (such as employees or someone with whom you have business dealings), you must ensure that you are entitled to disclose that Personal Information to us and that, without our taking any further steps, we may collect, use and disclose that Personal Information between GOVBID Entities on a confidential basis as described in this Privacy Policy. In particular, you must ensure that the individual concerned is aware of the various matters detailed in this Privacy Policy, as those matters relate to that individual, including our identity, how to contact us, our purposes of collection, our Personal Information disclosure practices and our Terms & Conditions. Any right the individual may have to obtain access to the Personal Information and make complaints about the handling of the Personal Information and the consequences if the Personal Information is not provided (such as our inability to provide services).

If any of the Personal Information that you have provided to us changes, for example if you change your email address or if you wish to cancel any request that you have made of us, please let us know by contacting GOVBID Customer Support through the GOVBID website at [https://govbid.org/tickets](https://govbid.org/login). GB CONTRACT TRADING LLC is not responsible or liable for any loss of data and will not be responsible for any losses arising from any inaccurate, inauthentic, deficient or incomplete Personal Information that you provide to us.

Data protection laws vary among countries, with some providing more protection than others. We maintain backup servers around the world and your information may be processed on servers located outside of the country where you live. Regardless of where your information is stored and processed, we apply the same protections described in this policy. We also comply with certain legal frameworks relating to data security and privacy.

With respect to European Economic Area (EEA) including United Kingdom (UK) residents and where your Personal Information is processed by an GOVBID Entity ("Business Clients Relations & International Representatives") established in the EEA ("Covered Individuals"), you have a number of legal rights under GDPR in relation to the Personal Information that we hold about you.

 _These rights include:_  

  * Requesting that we correct your personal information if it is inaccurate or incomplete.
  * Requesting that we erase your personal information in certain circumstances. Please note that there may be circumstances where you ask us to erase your personal information but we are legally entitled to retain it.
  * Retrieving information regarding the processing of your personal information and access to the personal information that we hold about you. Please note that there may be circumstances in which we are entitled to refuse requests for access to copies of personal information, (in particular, information that is subject to fraud investigations).
  * Objecting to, and requesting that we restrict, our processing of your personal information in certain circumstances. Please note that there may be circumstances where you object to, or ask us to restrict, our processing of your personal information but we are legally entitled to refuse that request.
  * Objecting to, and requesting that we dismiss active investigations or takedown, your personal information (username) that may be listed on our G.B.P Fraud Prevention Channels. Again, there may be circumstances where you object to, or ask us to dismiss, our investigation on your personal information (username) being listed but we are legally entitled to refuse that request.
  * Withdrawing your consent, although in certain circumstances it may be lawful for us to continue processing without your consent if we have another legitimate reason (other than consent) for doing so.
  * We have designated a Data Protection Officer ("DPO") to enhance and promote compliance with and understanding of privacy and data protection principles. If you wish to do any of the above please let us know by contacting GOVBID Customer Support through the GOVBID website at <https://govbid.org/contact_us>.

We reserve the right to update and change this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without your explicit consent. We always indicate the date when the last changes were published. If changes are significant, we’ll provide a more prominent notice through different channels, for example, posting a notice on our website or sending you a direct system or email notification.

If you have any privacy complaints or issues and want to contact GOVBID Data Protection Officer (DPO), please let us know by contacting GOVBID Customer Support through the GOVBID website at <https://govbid.org/contact_us>

This Privacy Policy was last updated on Sep 28, 2019. 

**5-Star RATED** Customer Assistance

2,186

MORE THAN  CLIENTS WORLDWIDE

The client’s full name, IP or physical address are never displayed publicly on the website other than within the user's profile interface itself. The only information that may be displayed openly is live contracts bidding feed (direct blockchain operation link may be attached), which may include operation’s time and date, amount of Digital Assets, and user's nickname.
